<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Hello | HackConf]]></title>
  <link href="http://hackconf.in/blog/categories/hello/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://hackconf.in/"/>
  <updated>2014-02-14T06:25:01+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://hackconf.in/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Navya]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[discuss@hackconf.in]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show Us Some Love!]]></title>
    <link href="http://hackconf.in/blog/2014/02/14/show-us-some-love/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-14T04:52:03+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://hackconf.in/blog/2014/02/14/show-us-some-love</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>What better day than the Valentine’s to ask for love! Today we are doing our
first public announcement and asking the community to help us out. We are self
motivated hackers who want to provide ourselves with a platform to connect to
other hackers like us and  help the new community members to be better hackers.
With this vision, a bunch of us came together with the idea of HackConf! We
count ourselves among you, which is the reason we have the tagline:
Unconference for, by and of you.</p>

<p>IIT Kanpur is known for its F/OSS conference,
<a href="http://arunraghavan.net/2008/01/fosskriti/">FOSSKriti</a>, which has sadly not
been revived for past couple of years. We tried to revive it this year, but due
to certain constraints we couldn&rsquo;t see it happening again. This did not stop us
from thinking big, we are now going the ‘Open’ way and trying to organize an
unconference with community support! The main goals of organizing HackConf has
been described in our Mission and Vision, if you support and believe in it,
then we ask you to be part of our team and help others like yourself! We have a
public repository hosted on Github, which you can fork away and send pull
requests! We need all the help we can get, we would appreciate any kind of
contribution towards making HackConf possible!</p>

<p>To begin with, we have some
<a href="https://github.com/navya/hackconf/issues?state=open">open issues</a> lingering on
Github, please check it out and see if you can fix the issue! We understand
that we might have missed some very basic things, since it is our first attempt
at hosting such a conference, which the experienced amongst you can let us know
by opening up an issue. We have set up
<a href="/contact/">community interaction tools</a> on various platforms, feel free to
join the discussion on any of the platforms. We are almost always available on
<a href="irc://irc.freenode.net/hackconf">irc</a> and
<a href="http://lists.hackconf.in/">mailing lists</a>! Looking forward for a successful
valentine’s!</p>

<p>Will you be HackConf’s valentine?</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
